[{"answer": "Death.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "What's the appropriate punishment for this guy?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing is, do they have an obligation to say something about guns.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Why is it that both the president and the man who wants to be president are saying nothing about guns?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I would take it one step further.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Why do so many Americans not feel angry enough to demand further gun control?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, it has been a tradition of and it's enshrined in our Constitution, the Second Amendment, the right to bear arms.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Is that a natural place to start with this debate?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "So what are we going to do, stop trying to fight terrorists?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, my --", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What is your personal interpretation?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I wasn't there but we have a mechanism under our Constitution that the founding fathers put in to answer exactly that question.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What do you think the founding fathers intended?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "You can't stop everything but you can stop most of it.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "If I wanted to buy an assault weapon and a load of ammunition on the Internet, for example, and I lived in New York, even with the laws that you have, and they're more stringent than many places in America, if you got anywhere stopping me?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, my own thing is if you look at where these attacks have occurred, there's one common factor.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, that's the reason I brought up the point that I did before.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Who stops this happening?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "There'd be no gun crime but there'll be other types of crime.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "But presumably you would accept if there were no guns at all in America there would be no gun crime, right?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "No, I don't think that's true.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Do you accept that America has the worst incidents of gun murders of any of what they call the civilized world?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "No, I mean, factually, it's not true.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "They are not true?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "But it is, isn't it?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "No, look, the murder rate right now -- or in the U.K. is low compared to the United States.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How do you say you don't have a particular problem here?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Two murders in London --", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How many murders there in 1900?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Look.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "At what point does your premise, more guns, less crime, look ridiculous?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, we just heard the worst kind of junk science that's being pushed by the most extreme lobby group in the United States, the National Rifle Association, which if it had its way, there would be no restrictions at all.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "OK, you want me to answer?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Answer my question.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Do you understand what the difference between a semi- automatic and automatic weapon is?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Sir, please, let me finish.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Why does anybody need to have a gun that can fire that number of bullets?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Because he pulled the trigger many times.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "How did he fire off so many rounds then?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Can I --", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "You are quite happy for other people to go into stores and buy the same weapon with the same magazine drum that can fire off up to 100 rounds a minute?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I'm done.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Are you done?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "No, Israel has very strict arms control --", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Israel's not a liberty loving country?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Only when the guest is talking complete nonsense.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "-- show where you talk most of the time?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "We've tried your way for too long.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "She's doing OK.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How is Faris, your daughter?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, first, it was amazement that -- I thought it was just part of the movie.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Just briefly tell me what the experience was like for you when this killer started?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, my feelings were -- I was all for hearing the charges that was going to go against him.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "What were your feelings about the court appearance today?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Sometimes yes, sometimes not.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Would somebody of that age, if they are genuinely schizophrenic -- would they be in control of what they're doing?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "If you want to look at can we make movie theaters safer, you can always harden the security around these places.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Is there anything more that can be done to prevent this kind of incident happening again?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "He didn't do anything to trigger anything.", "docId": "120723pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Do you feel comfortable that this guy could go and buy all this ammunition, all these weapons, all this protective gear, and do so perfectly legally without anyone picking him up?", "qSentId": 730}]